Guide to the California Asian American Artists Biographical Survey Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Reference Files, Series 4
  - Collections, Subseries 8
    - Archives of American Art: Ferdinand Perret Files (Calif Artists 1769-1942) (Box 4, Folder 18)
      Photocopy of cardfile info housed in the Archives of American Art.
    - San Francisco Public Library-photos from SF History Photo Collection (Box 4, Folder 19)
      Printouts of San Francisco Chinatown photographs.
  - Miscellaneous, Subseries 9
    - Chinese Six Company info (Box 4, Folder 20)
      Articles, student research report.
    - Parilia (San Francisco Art Association) (Box 4, Folder 21)
      Newspaper articles, photo.
    - Artists in Boston (Box 4, Folder 22)
      Article, student report, translation of info from Japanese book.
    - New York artists (general) (Box 4, Folder 23)
      Articles, translation of info from Japanese book.
    - Walt Disney artists/ Film general (Box 4, Folder 24)
      Articles, notes.
    - Central Valley Chinese American history (Box 4, Folder 25)
      Articles, student reports.
    - Gardeners (Bonsai) (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - South Asian California pioneers (Box 4, Folder 27)
      Exhibition catalog, photocopies of photos.
    - Archives of American Art, Asian American art resources (Box 4, Folder 28)
      Resource list compiled by AAA.
    - Historic SF Chinatown photos (Box 4, Folder 29)
      Images downloaded from web.
    - Brush painting (general) (Box 4, Folder 30)
      Misc. resources, exhibition announcements, etc.
    - Unidentified artists (Box 4, Folder 31)
      Copies of 1880 census records with unidentified "painters", unidentified students in Otis College class photo in 1925.
    - Buddhism (Box 4, Folder 32)
      Resource list for Buddhism-west coast art relationship; "Zen and Modern Art" exhibition brochure.
    - Filipino American art and history resources (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Misc. articles, exhibition info, Filipino American contact list.
    - Filipino American art and history resources (Box 7, Folder 2)
      Videotape of 1994 exhibition "5 Pioneers of Filipino American Art"
  - San Francisco Art Association Annual Exhibitions (later known as Oil, Tempera and Sculpture Exhib.), Subseries 10
    - 1916 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Photocopies of pages that include names of exhibiting Asian American artists.
    - 43rd Annual, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - 44th Annual, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - 45th Annual, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - 46th Annual, 1922-23 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - 47th Annual, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - 48th Annual, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - 49th Annual, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - 50th Annual, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - 51st Annual, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - 52nd Annual, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - 53rd Annual, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - 54th Annual, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - 55th Annual, 1935 (SFMA Inaugural) (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - 56th Annual, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - 57th Annual, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - 58th Annual, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - 59th Annual, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - 60th Annual, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - 61st Annual, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - 62nd Annual, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - 64th Annual, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - 65th Annual, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - 66th Annual, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - 67th Annual, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - 68th Annual, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - 69th Annual, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - 70th Annual, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - 71st Annual, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - 72nd Annual, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - 73rd Annual, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - 74th Annual, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - 75th Annual, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - 76th Annual, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - 77th Annual, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - 78th Annual, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - 79th Annual, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - San Francisco Art Association Annual Drawings, Prints Exhibitions, Subseries 11
    - 1st Annual, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - 2nd Annual, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - 3rd Annual, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - 4th Annual, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - 5th Annual, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - 6th Annual, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - 7th Annual, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - 8th Annual, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - 9th Annual, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - 10th Annual, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - 11th Annual, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - 12th Annual, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - 13th Annual, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - 14th Annual, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - 15th Annual, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - 16th Annual, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - 17th Annual, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - 18th Annual, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - 19th Annual, 1955-56 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - 20th Annual, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - 21st Annual, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - 22nd Annual, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - 23rd Annual, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - 24th Annual, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - 25th Annual, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - San Francisco Art Association Annual Watercolor Exhibitions, Subseries 12
    - 1st Annual, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - 2nd Annual, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - 3rd Annual, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - 4th Annual, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - 5th Annual, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - 6th Annual, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - 7th Annual, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - 8th Annual, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - 9th Annual, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - 10th Annual, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - 11th Annual, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - 12th Annual, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - 13th Annual, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - 14th Annual, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - 15th Annual, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - 16th Annual, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - 17th Annual, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - 18th Annual, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - 19th Annual, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous San Francisco Art Association and Other Exhibitions, Subseries 13
    - Misc. Japanese art events, San Francisco Institute of Art (Box 6, Folder 9)
      ca. 1909 and 1910 announcements for recpeption events.
    - SFAA Jury Free Summer Exhibition, California Artists, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - 3rd Annual SFAA Jury Free Exhibition, California Artists, 1921 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Art of Our Time, 10th Annual exhibition, San Francisco Museum of Art, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - 5th Annual Art Festival, Palace of Fine Arts, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Art Treasures from Japan, de Young Museum, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Contemporary Japanese Painting, 1952, California Palace of the Legion of Honor (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - 7th Annual Art Festival, Union Square, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - 12th Annual Art Festival, Fisherman's Wharf, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Paintings and Sculptures in the San Francisco Art Association (a catalog of the Art Bank of the SFAA), 1958 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - San Francisco Art Association Painting and Sculpture (catalog of the Art Bank of the SFAA), 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Asian American Art: A History, 1850-1970, Subseries 14
    - Asian American Art: A History, 1850-1970 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      book, Asian American Art: A History, 1850-1970